thedatingdivas.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy - The Dating Divas

### **The Dating Divas respect your privacy.**

##  ** _What Do You Do with My Information?_**

The Dating Divas, LLC (“The Dating Divas”) operates www.TheDatingDivas.com and may operate other websites. The Dating Divas is operated entirely within the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that any information – including personal data – that we collect about you will be transferred to and processed in the United States. You hereby consent to these transfers.

It is The Dating Divas’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites, and to use responsible practices in the collection, maintenance and use of your personal information.

When you use any website operated by The Dating Divas, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and The Dating Divas will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this privacy policy, you must discontinue use of any website of The Dating Divas and otherwise comply with the terms herein.

This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service, www.TheDatingDivas.com, owned and operated by The Dating Divas. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our customers have engaged us.

##  ** _How We Process Data_**

The following, along with our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.thedatingdivas.com/terms-disclosures/), contains information about how we process data.  In the event there is any conflict between the Terms and Conditions and these rules, these rules govern.

By use of The Dating Divas’ services, you instruct The Dating Divas to process any personal data you provide to The Dating Divas and agree to the processing of any personal data that The Dating Divas provides to you in connection with the services. You also specifically authorize the engagement of The Dating Divas’ Affiliates as sub-processors, including Infusionsoft. In addition, you generally authorize the engagement of any other third parties as sub-processors.

##  **Customer Obligations**

By use of The Dating Divas services you agree to comply with data protection, security and other obligations with respect to any and all personal data by adhering to this Privacy Policy and the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.thedatingdivas.com/terms-disclosures/) along with all local data protection laws to which you are subject. Any child under the age of sixteen must have parental consent to operate this site or to contacted by The Dating Divas.  The Dating Divas will inform you if, in The Dating Divas’ opinion, you have violated any data processing obligation.

##  **Details of Data Processing**

 _Subject Matter_ **:**  The Dating Divas’ services, customer provided data, and related technical support to customer, and the like.

 _Duration of the Processing_ **:**  The Dating Divas will not keep any personal information that we process for longer than is necessary for our stated purposes.

 _Nature and Purpose of the Processing_ **:**  The Dating Divas provides a website and related marketing platform and other related services as identified herein and in our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.thedatingdivas.com/terms-disclosures/).

 _Categories of Data_ **:**  As outlined in herein (“I Am An Affiliate of The Dating Divas,” “I Am A Subscriber To An Email List Managed Through The Dating Divas,” and “I Am A Customer or User of The Dating Divas.”)

 _Data Subjects_ **:**  Personal data submitted, stored, sent or received via The Dating Divas services that may concern the customer.

##  **Data Security**

The Dating Divas takes all reasonable technical and organizational measures to commit to confidentiality of your data including:

  1. Use of encryption
  2. Continual monitoring of the confidentiality, integrity, availability, and resilience of our systems
  3. Preparedness to restore availability of our services in the event of a physical or technical incident
  4. Regular risk assessments of all systems
  5. Commercially reasonable steps to ensure all those acting on The Dating Divas’ behalf maintain confidentiality of personal data
  6. Privacy confirmations of all sub-processors engaged in providing The Dating Divas services
  7. Provide written responses to all reasonable requests for information made by customers
  8. Reasonably assist customers with data security audits, including inspections, conducted by the customer, auditors, or other supervisory authorities
  9. Provide notice to customers regarding personal data breaches

##  **Data Rights**

 _Right to be informed_ **:**  You can ask about personal data, how it is used, and why it is being used at any time.

 _Right of access_ **:**  As outlined herein (“Access to Personal Information”).

 _Right of rectification_ **:**  You can update or request updates to personal information at any time.

 _Right of erasure_ **:**  You may cancel your The Dating Divas’ account, subscription, and the like at any time and may additionally request that The Dating Divas erase your personal data, cease further dissemination of the data, and potentially have third parties halt processing of the data. The Dating Divas reserves the right to keep the minimum amount of information that helps us prevent fraud to keep your deliverability as high as possible.

 _Right to restrict processing_ **:**  You may put your account, subscription, or the like on hold at any time which restricts said deliverability. Your data will still be processed for other actions such as billing and by our sub-processors. You may cancel your account, subscriptions, or the like to restrict all data processing of your data and reactivate your account as long as we have not yet deleted your information according to our retention policies.

 _Right to data portability_ **:**  You may request that your personal data be provided to you in a structured and commonly used format at any time as long as we have not yet deleted your information according to our retention policies.

 _Right to object_ **:**  You may unsubscribe from any of The Dating Divas’ emails, newsletters and the like at any time.

##  ** _What We Do And Do Not Do With any Information You Provide to Us_**

 **“I Am An Affiliate of The Dating Divas.”**

Your name, address, phone and fax number, email address, tax ID number or SSN and any other information you provide are held in strict confidence. We collect this information only so we can generate your commission checks and meet United States federal tax requirements.

We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

 **“I Am A Subscriber to An Email List Managed Through The Dating Divas.”**

Your email address, name and any other information you provide, such as address and phone number, are held in strict confidence. We only keep your information so that we can email our subscribers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected.

We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

If you no longer would like to be contacted by The Dating Divas, please contact us.

We acknowledge that you have the right to access your personal information. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his or her query to our us. If you request that we remove the data, we will respond to your request within 30 business days.

We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions. We will retain personal data we process for as long as needed in order to provide services to our customers. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##  **Newsletters**

The Dating Divas will subscribe you to our newsletter(s) only if you opt in.  We will use your name and email address, along with other information, to send the newsletter to you. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in each of the communications you receive.

##  **Service Related Emails**

We may also send you service related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not “promotional in nature.”

 **“I Am A Customer of The Dating Divas.”**

All account information for our customers is held in strict confidence.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described herein. We do not sell or share your information with anyone. We only collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information so we can provide the email and marketing services described on our website.

##  **Service Providers**

We use other third parties, such as a credit card processing company, to bill you for services, companies to process orders, and we also use advertisements to promote certain products. When you sign up for or purchase our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

##  **Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

##  **Access To Personal Information**

We will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information upon request. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##  **Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as login credentials and credit card information, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us.

##  ** _What About Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?_**

 **What are Cookies?**

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by our website. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows us, our partners, affiliates, and other service providers to recognize you and make your next visit easier and our service more useful to you.

 **How The Dating Divas uses Cookies**

We and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or services providers use technologies, such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer our website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember your settings (e.g., language preference), and for authentication.

 **Your choices regarding The Dating Divas Cookies**

You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. If you would like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

##  **What About HTML 5?  **

We use local storage such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML 5 and Flash cookies, to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

##  **What About Log Files?**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends, administer our website, track visitors’ movements around our website, and gather demographic information about our visitors as a whole. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about our website visitors.

##  **Advertising**

We partner with a third-party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other websites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on our website, as well as other websites, to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.

If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, please visit the help pages of your web browser.  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You may continue to receive generic ads.

##  **Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our website, which may contain personal information. We do obtain your consent to post your name along with your testimonial via email prior to posting the testimonial on our website. However, if you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, please contact us.

##  **Social Media Features**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our website. It may also set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

##  **Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We may update our privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

##  **Links to Other Sites**

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by our website.

##  **Public Forums**

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.  Our policies regarding commenting on our website can be found in our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.thedatingdivas.com/terms-disclosures/).

##  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via email at [support@thedatingdivas.zendesk.com](mailto:support@thedatingdivas.zendesk.com) or via postal mail at The Dating Divas, LLC, P.O. Box 2350, Parker, CO 80134, USA.
